Guide to the Horticultural Society of New York Records 1811-circa 2010 (bulk, 1900-circa 2010) MS 3033
New-York Historical Society
- Series IX. Memorabilia, 1900s-1998; 4.25 Linear feet
  - Medals: Blank (16), n.d. (Offsite-box 83, Object 5)
    Sixteen copies of a medal (14 bronze, 2 gold) with a blank reverse and "HORTICULTURAL SOCIETY OF NEW YORK | 1902" seal on obverse.
  - Printing plates (2), n.d. (Offsite-box 83, Object 6-7)
    Two small woodblock printing plates, one with Horticultural Society of New York seal, the other with logo for "People for Trees | Trees for People" (see box FF-13, folder 2, for lapel pin with same design).
  - Award: plaque [Oversize], 1998 April (Offsite-box 84, Object 1)
    GREENBRANCHES-SARATOGA BRANCH | LIBRARY PARTNERSHIP PROJECT | OF THE HORTICULTURAL SOCIETY OF N.Y. | BROOKLYN PUBLIC LIBRARY & BROOKLYN BOTANIC GARDEN | APRIL 1998.
    With reproduction of Linda Locke's article, "A Branch Blooms in Brooklyn," from the April 1998 issue of American Libraries: The Magazine of the American Library Association.
  - Photographic slide carousels (2) [Oversize], 1960s-1970s (Offsite-box 84, Object 2-3)
    Two empty Kodak photographic slide carousel trays in their boxes, one marked "BPFS" for "Bryant Park Flower Show." The slides may be found in Subseries III.C.
  - Photographic lantern slide cases (4) [Oversize], 1900s (Offsite-box 84, Object 4-7)
    Four empty boxes (one is a leather-like case, three are wood) that held the photographic lantern slides found in Subseries III.C and V.E.